Another tool which is recommended but not required is known as Fritzing.
This tool will help you a lot.
Creating the visual diagram of your project, basically.
So whatever project you are creating first, you can create its diagram.
So this diagram will help you create your easily create your jumper wires during your practical work
with your breadboard and Arduino Uno.
Right?
So this tool will help you a lot by creating visual diagram.
You can refer to this diagram when you will be creating the practical thing with your Arduino, Right?
So all the things which you are doing with jumper wires and the module you are using, you can refer
to this diagram first and then you can create your tool, right?
So this is the tool which we are going to use.
So I have already downloaded this tool.
This tool provides a zip folder.
So let's just go into that folder and let's just extract it.
So you don't need to install this tool.
You can just start it right away.
And when the tool first starts, it will ask you to update.
So you will you have to update this tool with all the components in it.
So we can start this tool.
Right.
So this is the pride board.
And we can.
Place ardino over here.
And the tool which we are going to use is known as RC 5 to 2.
Now, if you search RC 5 to 2, you will not find that tool.
What you have to do is you have to go into mine and then you have to click that small button over here
and click on import.
And you can find this RC 5 to 2 diagram which we have created in your resources file.
So all you have to do is you have to import this diagram and then you can use this diagram, right?
So this is the diagram which we are going to use RC 5 to 2
and we can create our connection with it, as you can see over here.
So after creating the connection, you can save the file as PNG or export the file as PNG or Jpeg,
whatever format you prefer, and you can refer to this diagram when you will be creating this actual
tool using jumper wires and breadboards.
So this diagram will help you a lot because uh, doing practically is little difficult, so you should
know what wire you are placing where.
So this diagram will help you a lot, right?
So you can save the diagram and share it whatever you want to do.